Hi everyone. This is Ravi. Welcome to my
YouTube channel.
So, Tricentis is
planning to release their new product
called Tricentis Device Cloud.
So, it is scheduled
to release on 8th of August.
So, in this session, I'm going to talk
more about this Tricentis
Device Cloud product, and what are all
the different advantages, and what are
all the different features that are
available in Tricentis Device Cloud.
Okay. So, coming to
introducing Tricentis Device Cloud.
So, it's a real mobile device testing
with cordless automation. So, basically,
by using this Tricentis Device Cloud,
you can perform your real mobile device
testing with
cordless automation tools.
In the digital age, around 80% of the
global population owns a smartphone, and
73% of the total e-commerce revenue is
generated from mobile devices.
So, whether you are developing mobile
apps for business-to-business, or
business-to-customer purposes,
delivering a seamless mobile experience
is critical for survival in today's
complex, competitive business
landscape.
So, in line with this demand, Tricentis
is thrilled to announce a new product
called Tricentis Device Cloud.
So, this new product reflects their
commitment to provide user-centric,
AI-powered, speedy, and highly efficient
mobile testing solutions that meet the
evolving needs of the digital landscape.
And what are all the different features
that are available in Tricentis Device
Cloud?
So, Tricentis Device Cloud is a real
mobile device farm that enables teams to
test on physical smartphones and tablets
in the cloud.
So, it includes
Apple iPhone, Samsung Galaxy, Google
Pixel, Oppo,
Find, Vivo, or Huawei and more. So,
Tricentis Device Cloud integrates
with both Tricentis Tosca and Tricentis
Testim for codeless end-to-end test
automation.
Such a capability empowers teams to
deliver flawless mobile applications
anywhere around the globe.
And
this Tricentis Device Cloud also works
on mobile artificial intelligence.
So, Tricentis Device Cloud is built
around a mobile AI engine
to help surface critical issues early
before end users notice.
So, using machine learning technology,
this engine processes extensive amounts
of data including object, image, text,
video, audio functionalities of mobile
applications to help pinpoint the issue.
And also, there is another
very good feature called performance
monitoring and user experience
analytics.
So, mobile users are notoriously
off So, mobile users are notorious for
quickly abandoning slow-loading content
mobile apps.
So, around 88% of users discard an app
if it's
slow or sluggish
with a poor user experience. Right? So,
addressing this challenge, the Tricentis
Device Cloud provides
holistic robust performance and user
experience analytics that tracks around
130 plus KPIs important to mobile apps.
So, it monitors network connectivity
or device metrics like battery usage,
memory, CPU usage, signal strength and
quality, and also audio-visual quality,
image modifications, right? Graphics,
animations, and more. So, Tricentis
Device Cloud empowers with rich
telemetry data over multiple runs and
builds
aiding application development teams in
detecting and immediately
rectifying errors that detrimentally
affect user experience and front-end
performance. So, this is one good
advantage that we have
by using Tricentis Device Cloud.
And also, consistency across web,
mobile, and desktop apps. So, by
integrating Tricentis Mobile and
Tricentis Device Cloud, teams can run
mobile, web, desktop, SAP, Salesforce,
and API testing within a unified flow,
thereby ensuring full coverage of your
regression portfolio.
So, this dynamic combination facilitates
functional, performance, and usability
testing to help enterprise teams deliver
impeccable mobile experiences across
their entire IT landscape.
And also, this
Tricentis Device Cloud, which means TDC,
right? Compatible across all devices,
operating systems, and browsers. So,
Tricentis Device Cloud offers you a
choice from an extensive selection of
physical devices, including smartphones,
tablets from brands like Apple, Samsung,
Google, Oppo, as I told you earlier, and
more. So, their end-to-end solution
enables automation testing of mobile
apps
across various devices, browsers, and
operating system combinations, providing
comprehensive coverage and significantly
speeding up testing while enabling
customers to scale rapidly.
So, these are all the different
advantages
that Tricentis is going to provide us
with Tricentis Device Cloud
product.
So, I'm going to publish two more videos
where
I'm going to show you hands-on
experience of this Tricentis Device
Cloud.
And also, I'm going to publish another
video where
I can show you how can you integrate
your Tosca or Testim. That means
Tricentis automation tool, Tosca, and
Tricentis SaaS platform-based Testim
automation tool, right? These two tools,
how can you integrate with this new
product called Tricentis Device Cloud?
And once you integrate with Tricentis
Device Cloud, how can you perform
automation testing on real devices that
are
configured in this
device cloud. I'm going to show you
hands-on
with two more videos. Then you will get
more information, and you will get what
are all the advantages that Device Cloud
is having over other cloud service
providers. Okay? So, please do subscribe
to channel. Click on the icon. You'll
receive notifications whenever I publish
more videos. Thank you.